Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1992-1993.
  - Local 19, 1992-1993; 17 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00744 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 20, 1992-1993; 18 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00822 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 21, 1992-1993; 19 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00827 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 24, 1992-1993; 20 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 00854 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 25, 1992-1993; 21 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01010 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 26, 1992-1993; 22 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01053 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 29, 1992-1993; 23 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01110 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 30, 1992-1993; 24 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01111 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 31, 1992-1993; 25 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01139 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 32, 1992-1993; 26 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01178 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 34, 1992-1993; 27 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01200 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 35, 1992-1993; 28 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01236 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 36, 1992-1993; 29 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01253 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 37, 1992-1993; 30 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01258 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 40, 1992-1993; 31 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01308 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 43, 1992-1993; 32 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01361 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 47, 1992-1993; 33 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01378 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 49, 1992-1993; 34 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01458 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 51, 1992-1993; 35 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01483 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 54, 1992-1993; 36 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01500 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 56, 1992-1993; 37 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01694 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 57, 1992-1993; 38 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01704 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 62, 1992-1993; 39 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01745 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 64, 1992-1993; 40 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01787 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 65, 1992-1993; 41 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01797 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 69, 1992-1993; 42 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01806 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 72, 1992-1993; 43 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01823 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 73, 1992-1993; 44 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01831 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 74, 1992-1993; 45 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01859 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 75, 1992-1993; 46 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01889 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 76, 1992-1993; 47 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01903 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 77, 1992-1993; 48 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01905 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 84, 1992-1993; 49 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01926 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 86, 1992-1993; 50 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01942 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 99, 1992-1993; 51 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01984 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 100, 1992; 52 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 01998 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 100, 1993; 53 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02062 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 100. Trusteeship., 1992-1993; 54 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02179 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 100. Palios Restaurant., 1992-1993; 55 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02515 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 101, 1992-1993; 56 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02655 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 104, 1992-1993; 57 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02659 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 118, 1992-1993; 58 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02676 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 122, 1992-1993; 59 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02689 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 126, 1992-1993; 60 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02703 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 146, 1992-1993; 61 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02705 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 150, 1992-1993; 62 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02707 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 151, 1992-1993; 63 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02709 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 155, 1992-1993; 64 (Reel 54)
    Beginning at frame 02730 on Correspondence reel 15.
  - Local 165, 1992-1993; 1 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 02752 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 166, 1992-1993; 2 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 181, 1992-1993; 3 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00021 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 200, 1992-1993; 4 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00043 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 206, 1992-1993; 5 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00056 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 215, 1992-1993; 6 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00068 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 217, 1992-1993; 7 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00072 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 225, 1992-1993; 8 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00144 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 226, 1992; 9 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00153 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 226, 1993; 10 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00353 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 246, 1992-1993; 11 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00436 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 251, 1992-1993; 12 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00450 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 261, 1992-1993; 13 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00468 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 264, 1992-1993; 14 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00487 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 270, 1992-1993; 15 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00501 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 272, 1992-1993; 16 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00527 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 274, 1992-1993; 17 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00537 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 300, 1992-1993; 18 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00551 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 301, 1992-1993; 19 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00569 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 309, 1992-1993; 20 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00605 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 310, 1992-1993; 21 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00629 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 315, 1992-1993; 22 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00631 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 332, 1992-1993; 23 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00633 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 340, 1992-1993; 24 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00637 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 353, 1992-1993; 25 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00646 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 355, 1992-1993; 26 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00663 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 360, 1992-1993; 27 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00758 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 361, 1992-1993; 28 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00775 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 369, 1992-1993; 29 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00778 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 391, 1992-1993; 30 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00785 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 400, 1992-1993; 31 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00797 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 401. Hospital and Nursing Home Council., 1992-1993; 32 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00802 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 414, 1992-1993; 33 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00808 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 427, 1992-1993; 34 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00813 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 442, 1992-1993; 35 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00848 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 450, 1992-1993; 36 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00873 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 457, 1992-1993; 37 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00883 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 466, 1992-1993; 38 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00893 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 471, 1992-1993; 39 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00897 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 479, 1992-1993; 40 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00911 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 483, 1992-1993; 41 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00918 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 497, 1992-1993; 42 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00926 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 498, 1992-1993; 43 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00934 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 517, 1992-1993; 44 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00944 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 531, 1992-1993; 45 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00950 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 535, 1992-1993; 46 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00956 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 535. H. & W. Correspondence., 1992-1993; 47 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00959 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 550, 1992-1993; 48 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 00997 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 590, 1992-1993; 49 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01025 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 604, 1992-1993; 50 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01028 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 610, 1992-1993; 51 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01031 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 611, 1992-1993; 52 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01054 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 623, 1992-1993; 53 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01089 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 628, 1992-1993; 54 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01093 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 631, 1992-1993; 55 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01129 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 634, 1992-1993; 56 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01167 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 662, 1992-1993; 57 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01191 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 681, 1992-1993; 58 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01214 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 688, 1992-1993; 59 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01240 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 703, 1992-1993; 60 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01252 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 719, 1992-1993; 61 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01279 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 727, 1992-1993; 62 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01287 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 737, 1992-1993; 63 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01293 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 772, 1992-1993; 64 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01313 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 775, 1992-1993; 65 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01324 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 779, 1992-1993; 66 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01346 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 791, 1992-1993; 67 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01459 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 803, 1992-1993; 68 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01366 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 803. Uniserv Correspondence., 1992-1993; 69 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01376 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 804, 1992-1993; 70 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01490 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 814, 1992-1993; 71 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01499 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 847, 1992-1993; 72 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01623 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 863, 1992-1993; 73 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01632 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 878, 1992-1993; 74 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01653 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 879, 1992-1993; 75 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01670 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Local 28 & Local 50, 1992-1993; 76 (Reel 55)
    Beginning at frame 01688 on Correspondence reel 16.
  - Duplicate of Correspondence reel 1 (see reel 40), 1 (Reel 56)
  - Duplicate of Correspondence reel 2 (see reel 41), 1 (Reel 57)
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous.
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 7., 1 (Reel 58)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 8., 1 (Reel 59)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 9., 1 (Reel 60)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 10., 1 (Reel 61)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 11., 1 (Reel 62)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 12., 1 (Reel 63)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 13., 1 (Reel 64)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 14., 1 (Reel 65)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 15., 1 (Reel 66)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 16., 1 (Reel 67)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 17., 1 (Reel 68)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 18., 1 (Reel 69)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 19., 1 (Reel 70)
  - G. S. T. Miscellaneous reel 20., 1 (Reel 71)